http://www.homeeducatorsresource.com/content/privacy-notice

Home
Shopping Cart
My Account
Checkout
View your shopping cart.
Solr Search Block
Enter your keywords:
Privacy Notice Table Of Contents
Our Commitment To Privacy The Information We Collect How We Use Information Our Commitment To Data Security Our Commitment To Children's Privacy How To Access Or Correct Your Information How To Contact Us
Our Commitment To Privacy
Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice
explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way
your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it
available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information
may be requested.
The Information We Collect
This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on the Home Educator's
Resource website. On some pages, you can order products, make requests, and register to
receive materials. The types of personal information collected at these pages
are:
Name Address Email address Phone number Credit/Debit Card Information (etc.)
On some pages, you can submit information about other people. For example, if you
order a book online and want it sent directly to the recipient, you will need to submit
the recipient's address. In this circumstance, the types of personal information
collected are:
Name Address Phone Number (etc.)
The Way We Use Information
We use the information you provide about yourself when placing an order only to
complete that order. We do not share this information with outside parties except to
the extent necessary to complete that order.
We use the information you provide about someone else when placing an order only to
ship the product and to confirm delivery. We do not share this information with outside
parties except to the extent necessary to complete that order.
We offer gift-cards by which you can personalize a product you order for another
person. Information you provide to us to create a gift-card is only used for that
purpose, and it is only disclosed to the person receiving the gift.
We use return email addresses to answer the email we receive. Such addresses are not
used for any other purpose and are not shared with outside parties.
You can register with our website if you would like to receive discou as well as
updates on our new products and services. Information you submit on our website will
not be used for this purpose unless you fill out the registration form.
We use non-identifying and aggregate information to better design our website and to
share with advertisers. For example, we may tell an advertiser that X number of
individuals visited a certain area on our website, or that Y number of men and Z number
of women filled out our registration form, but we would not disclose anything that
could be used to identify those individuals.
Finally, we never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us
online in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you an
opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses.
Our Commitment To Data Security
To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of
information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial
procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.
Our Commitment To Children's Privacy
Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, we
never collect or maintain information at our website from those we actually know are
under 13, and no part of our website is structured to attract anyone under 13.
How You Can Access Or Correct Your Information
You can access all your personally identifiable information that we collect online and
maintain by logging in to your account. We use this procedure to better safeguard your
information.
You can correct factual errors in your personally identifiable information by sending
us a request that credibly shows error.
To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your
identity before granting access or making corrections.
How To Contact Us
Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please
contact us by filling out our Contact Us form here. Please be very specific as to why you are contacting us. Thank
you.
Landmark Prep Classes
Math Skills
Pre-Algebra
Algebra 1
Algebra 2
Geometry
Trigonometry/Precalculus
SAT/ACT Math Prep
Spanish 2
Product Categories:
Coloring BookEnrichmnt Cl CaForeign LanguaKonosLandmark PrepaMaster BooksPhysicsVisuals GrammaCollege PrepKeyboardingMoney ManagemMontessori MaterialsStudy GuidesLiterature GuideReference ForeLANDMARK PREP CLASSESHistory ClassScience ClassesShow All LANDMARK PREP CLASSESReference PrekSing Spell Read WritApologeticsCharacterChristian Liberty PresComputersGovernmentMath CurriculumMystery Of HistoryParentingReferenceUnit StudyWeekly SpecialsAbekaAlpha OmegaBible Homeschool Curriculum01st Grade Bible Curriculum02nd Grade Bible Curriculum03rd Grade Bible Curriculum04th Grade Bible Curriculum05th Grade Bible Curriculum06th Grade Bible Curriculum07th Grade Bible Curriculum08th Grade Bible Curriculum09th Grade Bible Curriculum10th Grade Bible Curriculum11th Grade Bible Curriculum12th Grade Bible CurriculumBible ReferenceBible VisualsShow All Bible Homeschool CurriculumClassical Homeschool CurriculumVeritas PressShow All Classical Homeschool CurriculumCo-Op Book ListRichardson Co-Op Book ListSalt Co-Op Book ListShow All Co-Op Book ListEnglish Homeschool CurriculumEnglish Curriculum by Grade01st Grade English02nd Grade English03rd Grade English04th Grade English5th Grade English06th Grade English07th Grade English08th Grade English09th Grade English10th Grade English11th Grade English12th Grade EnglishEnglish VisualsKindergarten EnglishMulti-Level English CurriculumShow All English Curriculum by GradeGrammar Curriculum by GradeGrammar ReferenceMulti-Level Grammar CurriculumShow All Grammar Curriculum by GradePhonics Curriculum by GradeKindergarten Phonics CurriculumPhonics CurriculumShow All Phonics Curriculum by GradeSpelling Curriculum by Grade01st Grade Spelling02nd Grade Spelling03rd Grade Spelling04th Grade Spelling05th Grade Spelling06th Grade Spelling08th Grade SpellingMulti-Level Spelling CurriculumShow All Spelling Curriculum by GradeVocabulary Curriculum by Grade01st Grade Vocabulary02nd Grade Vocabulary03rd Grade Vocabulary04th Grade Vocabulary05th Grade Vocabulary06th Grade Vocabulary07th Grade Vocabulary08th Grade Vocabulary09th Grade Vocabulary10th Grade Vocabulary11th Grade Vocabulary12th Grade VocabularyShow All Vocabulary Curriculum by GradeWriting Curriculum by Grade03rd Grade Writing09th Grade Writing10th Grade WritingMulti-Level Writing CurriculumShow All Writing Curriculum by GradeShow All English Homeschool CurriculumForeign Language CurriculumMulti-Level Foreign Language CurriculumShow All Foreign Language CurriculumGeography Homeschool CurriculumGraduation SuppliesHandwriting Homeschool Curriculum01st Grade Handwriting Curriculum02nd Grade Handwriting Curriculum03rd Grade Handwriting Curriculum04th Grade Handwriting Curriculum05th Grade Handwriting Curriculum06th Grade Handwriting CurriculumHandwriting VisualsKindergarten Handwriting CurriculumShow All Handwriting Homeschool CurriculumHealth Homeschool Curriculum01st Grade Health Curriculum02nd Grade Health Curriculum03rd Grade Health Curriculum04th Grade Health Curriculum05th Grade Health Curriculum07th Grade Health Curriculum08th Grade Health CurriculumHealth VisualsKindergarten Health CurriculumShow All Health Homeschool CurriculumHistory Homeschool Curriculum01st Grade History Curriculum02nd Grade History Curriculum03rd Grade History Curriculum04th Grade History Curriculum05th Grade History Curriculum06th Grade History Curriculum07th Grade History Curriculum08th Grade History Curriculum09th Grade History Curriculum10th Grade History Curriculum11th Grade History Curriculum12th Grade History CurriculumHistory ReferenceKindergarten HistoryShow All History Homeschool CurriculumHomeschool SuppliesTeacher SuppliesTesting SuppliesShow All Homeschool SuppliesKindergarten Homeschool CurriculumLiterature Homeschool Curriculum07th Grade Literature Curriculum08th Grade Literature Curriculum09th Grade Literature Curriculum10th Grade Literature Curriculum11th Grade Literature Curriculum12th Grade Literature CurriculumFive In A RowShow All Literature Homeschool CurriculumMath Homeschool Curriculum01st Grade Math02nd Grade Math03rd Grade Math04th Grade Math05th Grade Math06th Grade Math07th Grade Math08th Grade Math09th Grade Math10th Grade Math11th Grade Math12th Grade MathKindergarten Math CurriculumMath VisualsShow All Math Homeschool CurriculumMultimedia CurriculumAudio CurriculumSoftware CurriculumShow All Multimedia CurriculumMusic CurriculumMusic SuppliesShow All Music CurriculumNovels / Fiction BooksBeautiful Feet BooksFiction / Novel BooksSonlight CurriculumShow All Novels / Fiction BooksOVERSTOCKED PRODUCTSPrep School Book Reading ListCoram Deo Academy01st Grade Coram Deo Academy01st Grade Coram Deo Academy Summer Reading02nd Grade Coram Deo Academy03rd Grade Coram Deo Academy Summer Reading05th Grade Coram Deo Academy Summer Reading06th Grade Coram Deo Academy Summer Reading07th Grade Coram Deo Academy Summer Reading08th Grade Coram Deo Academy Summer Reading09th Grade Coram Deo Academy Summer Reading10th Grade Coram Deo Academy Summer Reading11th Grade Coram Deo Academy Summer Reading12th Grade Coram Deo Academy Summer ReadingKindergarten Coram Deo AcademyElectives CDaShow All Coram Deo AcademyDenton Calvary Academy09th Grade Denton Calvary Academy10th Grade Denton Calvary Academy11th Grade Denton Calvary Academy12th Grade Denton Calvary AcademyKindergarten Denton Calvary Academy1st Grade Foun2nd Grade Foun3rd Grade Foun4 Grade Foundr5 Grade Foundr6 Grade Found7 Grade Found8 Grade Foundr9 Grade Foundr10 Grade Foundr11 Grade Foundr12 Grade FoundrKinder Lca1st Grade Lca2nd Grade LcaShow All Denton Calvary AcademyShow All Prep School Book Reading ListReading Homeschool Curriculum01st Grade Reading02nd Grade Reading03rd Grade Reading04th Grade Reading05th Grade Reading06th Grade ReadingKindergarten ReadingReadersReading VisualsShow All ReadersReading ComprehensionShow All Reading Homeschool CurriculumRod And StaffScience Homeschool Curriculum01st Grade Science02nd Grade Science03rd Grade Science04th Grade Science05th Grade Science06th Grade Science07th Grade Science08th Grade Science09th Grade Science10th Grade Science11th Grade Science12th Grade ScienceElementary Science CurriculumPre K / Kindergarten ScienceScience ReferenceShow All Science Homeschool CurriculumSpeech / Debate CurriculumUnit Studies CurriculumTapestry Show All Unit Studies CurriculumUnsorted Curriculum ResourcesVisuals / ManipulativesWorkbook Support
